notey.com 2016-04-17

# Notey - Privacy

Notey is founded on the principle of helping people discover new stories and bloggers. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Notey is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect and use information from and about Notey users, as well as how information contributes to building an interest based social network. 

By visiting the Notey website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this policy. 

##  What information do we collect and store? 

We collect and store information from you when you register with Notey, when you make contribution through notes, and when you add any information about Notey topics, and fill out forms. 

When registering on Notey, making a note, adding a new topic, related topic, or purchasing products or services through Notey, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may however, visit Notey anonymously. 

We may also collect your location when you post comments to provide refined search results when using the Notey. 

We may combine the information you submit under your Notey account with other Notey functions and features so as to provide you with a better experience. 

All users have the freedom to choose to whom they send notes in Notey. Any recipients of a note may be able to see some information about other Notey user who has received it. 

If you wish to not display your information on your profile, you may select the “private” setting. 

##  What do we use the information for? 

The information we collect from you may be used in the following way: 

To develop your profile within Notey, we may use the name you chose for your profile, plus notes and other content shared (i.e. topic albums and photos) to be available to other Notey users. 

To personalize your experience and ultimately respond to your individual needs for sharing topic information, we may use your list of topic preferences, your likes and dislikes set up at registration, in order to through suggesting topics that interest you, suggesting friends that may share the same interests, including the same likes and dislikes as you. 

To provide an enriched user experience within Notey, including Notey mobile applications, we may use your contributions of notes, topic and album and photo uploads to support the search, exploration and discovery of detailed and relevant topic information, relationships between other related topic information, and product or service information related to topics of social interest. 

To improve Notey. As we continually strive to improve our categories of topics, we may use the topic information and relationships we receive from you. 

To process your requests for 3rd party products or services related to topics of interest. 

To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your topics of interests, as well as general news, updates extra features and functionalities about Notey. 

To administer advertising for products and services related to topics of interest, and for the sake of improving your experience as mentioned in 1. – 4. above, your public information may be exchanged, transferred, sold, or given to any company. 

We may share aggregate statistics about Notey activity with the public, our users, and partners, such as topic page affiliates, Notey business users or connected accounts. 

##  How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of standard security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, appropriate to the nature of the information. 

##  Do we use cookies? 

We may send cookies to your computer or device, in order to improve the quality of Notey search results, as well as to provide a personalized user experience. We may also store data (such as recent notes) locally on your browser. 

##  Do we disclose any personal or sensitive information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or providing you with topic information, so as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information (6. above) may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. 

##  Third party links 

For your convenience and benefit, occasionally we may include offering third party products or services as part of the topic information provided within Notey. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sits. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity if Notey and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

##  Online privacy policy only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Notey website and mobile applications and not to information collected offline. 

##  Children under 13 

The Notey site is not intended for children under the age of 13. The Notey site includes unmonitored content added by Notey users and sourced from thirds parties. Some of this content may not be suitable for children, thus we do not knowingly collect or distribute information unsuitable for children under age of 13. 

##  Terms and conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.notey.com/terms.html. 

##  Your consent 

By using Notey, you consent to our privacy policy. If you disagree with anything in this privacy policy, you may not choose to use the Notey website and mobile applications. 

##  Deleting your Notey account 

If you wish, you may delete your Notey account and any associated information by emailing a request to info@notey.com. 

##  Changes to our privacy policy 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of Notey. 

##  Contacting us 

We are a small company and it is our goal to make Notey as engaging and useful as possible for its Users. If you feel we can improve this Privacy Policy to provide an enhanced experience or if there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us by emailing info@notey.com.
